Princeton Football Films Collection, 1935-2012(bulk 1935-1990): Finding Aid AC297
University Archives
- Princeton Football Film Reels, 1935-1990; 2187 items
  - 1978-1979, 201 items
    - 1979 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1979 Yale (Offense 2))
  - 1980-1981, 227 items
    - 1980 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Brown (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Full Game 1))
    - 1980 Brown (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Full Game 2))
    - 1980 Brown (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Full Game 3))
    - 1980 Brown (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Full Game 4))
    - 1980 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1980 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1980 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Colgate (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Colgate (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Colgate (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Full Game 1))
    - 1980 Colgate (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Full Game 2))
    - 1980 Colgate (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Full Game 3))
    - 1980 Colgate (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Full Game 4))
    - 1980 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1980 Colgate (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Kicking))
    - 1980 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Colgate (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Colgate (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Colgate (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1980 Columbia (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Full Game 2))
    - 1980 Columbia (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Full Game 3))
    - 1980 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1980 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1980 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1980 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1980 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1980 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1980 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1980 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1980 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1980 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Harvard (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Full Game 1))
    - 1980 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1980 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1980 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1980 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1980 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1980 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Maine (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Maine (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Maine (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Maine (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Maine (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Full Game 1))
    - 1980 Maine (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Full Game 2))
    - 1980 Maine (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Full Game 3))
    - 1980 Maine (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Kicking))
    - 1980 Maine (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Kicking))
    - 1980 Maine (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Maine (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Maine (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Maine (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Maine (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1980 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1980 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1980 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1980 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1980 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Full Game 1))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Full Game 2))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Full Game 3))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Kicking))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Kicking))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Rutgers (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Rutgers (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1980 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1980 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1980 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1980 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1980 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1980 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1980 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1980 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1980 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1980 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Army (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Army (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Army (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Army (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Army (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Full Game 3))
    - 1981 Army (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Full Game 4))
    - 1981 Army (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Kicking))
    - 1981 Army (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Kicking))
    - 1981 Army (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Army (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Army (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Army (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1981 Columbia (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1981 Columbia (Full Game 4))
    - 1981 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1981 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1981 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1981 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1981 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1981 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1981 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1981 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Delaware (Miscellaneous), 1 item (Item 1981 Delaware (Miscellaneous))
    - 1981 Deleware (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Deleware (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Deleware (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Deleware (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Deleware (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Deleware (Kicking))
    - 1981 Deleware (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Deleware (Kicking))
    - 1981 Deleware (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Deleware (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Deleware (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Deleware (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Deleware (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Deleware (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1981 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1981 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Lafayette (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Lafayette (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Lafayette (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Lafayette (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Lafayette (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Lafayette (Kicking))
    - 1981 Maine (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Maine (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Maine (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Maine (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Maine (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Kicking))
    - 1981 Maine (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Kicking))
    - 1981 Maine (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Maine (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Maine (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Maine (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Maine (Offense 2))
    - 1981 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1981 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1981 None (Practice/Scrimage), 1 item (Item 1981 None (Practice/Scrimage))
    - 1981 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1981 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1981 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1981 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1981 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1981 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1981 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1981 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1981 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1981 Yale (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Full Game 2))
    - 1981 Yale (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Full Game 3))
    - 1981 Yale (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Full Game 4))
    - 1981 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1981 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1981 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1981 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1981 Yale (Offense 2))
  - 1982-1983, 227 items
    - 1982 Army (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Army (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Army (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Army (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Army (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Full Game 1))
    - 1982 Army (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Full Game 3))
    - 1982 Army (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Kicking))
    - 1982 Army (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Kicking))
    - 1982 Army (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Army (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Army (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Army (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Army (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1982 Brown (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Kicking))
    - 1982 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Brown (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Brown (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Brown (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Columbia (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Columbia (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Columbia (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Full Game 1))
    - 1982 Columbia (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Kicking))
    - 1982 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Columbia (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Columbia (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Columbia (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Cornell (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Cornell (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Cornell (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Cornell (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Cornell (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Cornell (Full Game 1))
    - 1982 Cornell (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Cornell (Full Game 2))
    - 1982 Cornell (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1982 Cornell (Full Game 3))
    - 1982 Cornell (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1982 Cornell (Full Game 4))
    - 1982 Cornell (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Cornell (Kicking))
    - 1982 Cornell (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Cornell (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Cornell (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Cornell (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Full Game 1))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Full Game 2))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Full Game 3))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Full Game 4))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Kicking))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Dartmouth (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Dartmouth (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Delaware (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Delaware (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Delaware (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Delaware (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Delaware (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Delaware (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Delaware (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Delaware (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Delaware (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Delaware (Kicking))
    - 1982 Delaware (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Delaware (Kicking))
    - 1982 Delaware (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Delaware (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Delaware (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Delaware (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Delaware (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Delaware (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Harvard (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Harvard (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Harvard (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Full Game 2))
    - 1982 Harvard (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Full Game 3))
    - 1982 Harvard (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Full Game 4))
    - 1982 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1982 Harvard (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Kicking))
    - 1982 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Harvard (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Harvard (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Harvard (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Kicking))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Kicking))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Lafayette (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Lafayette (Offense 2))
    - 1982 None (Highlights), 1 item (Item 1982 None (Highlights))
    - 1982 Penn (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Penn (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Penn (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Full Game 1))
    - 1982 Penn (Full Game 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Full Game 2))
    - 1982 Penn (Full Game 3), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Full Game 3))
    - 1982 Penn (Full Game 4), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Full Game 4))
    - 1982 Penn (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Kicking))
    - 1982 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Penn (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Penn (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Penn (Offense), 1 item (Item 1982 Penn (Offense))
    - 1982 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Yale (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Defense 1))
    - 1982 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Yale (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Defense 2))
    - 1982 Yale (Full Game 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Full Game 1))
    - 1982 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1982 Yale (Kicking), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Kicking))
    - 1982 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Yale (Offense 1), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Offense 1))
    - 1982 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1982 Yale (Offense 2), 1 item (Item 1982 Yale (Offense 2))
    - 1983 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1983 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1983 Brown (Defense 1), 1 item (Item 1983 Brown (Defense 1))
    - 1983 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1983 Brown (Defense 2))
    - 1983 Brown (Defense 2), 1 item (Item 1983 Brown (Defense 2))